[
  {
    "question": "Where does Pierre Huyghe currently live?",
    "a": "Berlin",
    "b": "Tokyo",
    "c": "New York City",
    "d": "Paris",
    "e": "London",
    "correct_answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who commissioned The Third Memory?",
    "a": "The New Museum",
    "b": "The Renaissance Society",
    "c": "The Dia Art Foundation",
    "d": "The Mattress Factory",
    "e": "The Wexner Center for the Arts",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which bank was the victim of the heist featured in The Third Memory?",
    "a": "Citibank",
    "b": "Capital One Bank",
    "c": "Chase Bank",
    "d": "First American Bank",
    "e": "Bank of America",
    "correct_answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which actor starred in the film that The Third Memory drew scenes from?",
    "a": "Al Pacino",
    "b": "James Earl Jones",
    "c": "Robert DeNiro",
    "d": "Julia Roberts",
    "e": "Daniel Day-Lewis",
    "correct_answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where did Huyghe and Parreno first encounter the character Annlee?",
    "a": "as an advertisement mascot",
    "b": "in a Japanese children’s show",
    "c": "in an art festival they both visited",
    "d": "a mail-order catalog of characters",
    "e": "in a manga from Parreno’s childhood",
    "correct_answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "How did No Ghost Just a Shell end?",
    "a": "Huyghe and Parreno ended the tour of their work.",
    "b": "Huyghe and Parreno sold the rights to the character.",
    "c": "Huyghe and Parreno destroyed all copies of their work.",
    "d": "Huyghe and Parreno were sued by the character’s original creator.",
    "e": "Huyghe and Parreno stopped producing copies of their animation.",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which book does Smile without a Cat reference?",
    "a": "Charlotte’s Web",
    "b": "Tom Sawyer",
    "c": "The Jungle Book",
    "d": "Alice in Wonderland",
    "e": "Pinocchio",
    "correct_answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which medium did Pierre Huyghe PRIMARILY practice in during the beginning of his career?",
    "a": "film",
    "b": "acrylics",
    "c": "textiles",
    "d": "sculpture",
    "e": "engraving",
    "correct_answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which feature of a biennial exhibition separates it from a traditional art fair?",
    "a": "A biennial focuses specifically on sculpture.",
    "b": "A biennial is held in a significant city in art history.",
    "c": "The art is owned independently and not for sale.",
    "d": "The art is created live, rather than in advance.",
    "e": "A biennial is sponsored by an art academy.",
    "correct_answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following cities holds the most influential biennial exhibition?",
    "a": "Kyoto",
    "b": "Khulna",
    "c": "Singapore",
    "d": "Gwangju",
    "e": "Kochi",
    "correct_answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which historical event MOST directly contributed to the founding of the Kassel Documenta?",
    "a": "the Great Depression",
    "b": "the Russian Revolution",
    "c": "the Cold War",
    "d": "the fall of the Berlin Wall",
    "e": "World War 2",
    "correct_answer": "e"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which challenge would a visitor to Untilled MOST likely face?",
    "a": "The exhibit was entirely in Japanese.",
    "b": "The exhibit required participation.",
    "c": "The exhibit was difficult to find.",
    "d": "The exhibit was poorly lit.",
    "e": "The exhibit was only open briefly.",
    "correct_answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following elements was NOT a part of Untilled?",
    "a": "an oak tree",
    "b": "a live, white dog",
    "c": "piles of concrete bricks",
    "d": "a kettle drum",
    "e": "a sculpture of a nude woman",
    "correct_answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which element of Untilled was MOST consistent with Huyghe’s earlier work?",
    "a": "its incorporation of digital art",
    "b": "its focus on environmental activism",
    "c": "its themes of death and rebirth",
    "d": "its allusions to other artists",
    "e": "its incorporation of work not made by the artist",
    "correct_answer": "e"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artist was known for his pieces composed purely of found objects?",
    "a": "Wassily Kandinsky",
    "b": "Piet Mondrian",
    "c": "Henri Matisse",
    "d": "Pablo Picasso",
    "e": "Marcel Duchamp",
    "correct_answer": "e"
  }
]